Welcome to the Records Management simulation.
This short video will explain the different
sections and navigational buttons
in this simulation.
Each job also has specific directions and a video
walkthrough that will give you more details about
how to complete that job.
The How to Navigate records management video
that you are watching now,
describes the basic sections,
screens and buttons in this simulation.
The Overview of Auric Systems, Inc.
screen gives you background
information about the company in this simulation.
Depending on what job you are working in,
you will see either
“Overview of Jobs 1 through 4”
or “Overview of Jobs 5 through 13.”
The “Overview of Jobs 1 through 4” screen
gives you information about your role
in Auric Systems
and how to complete these first four jobs.
The Overview screen for Jobs 5 through 13
provides information about working with
correspondence in jobs 5 through 13.
Each job’s landing page has a Directions screen
specific to that job.
This screen gives you an overview of what
you will be doing in a specific job.
The video walkthrough for each job gives
detailed instructions on how to navigate
that job,
and how to complete the steps
in each task of that job.
After you have watched the video,
click the START JOB button.
For most jobs,
this will take you directly
to the main task screen for that job.
Some of the later jobs have more complicated
navigation,
with more than one main task screen
or with additional information provided
before you reach the main task screen.
For example,
this is the General Information
screen for Job 10.
Again, the Video Walkthrough for each job
will explain any navigation
that is specific to that job.
Clicking the Records Management logo
brings you back to the landing page
for the job you are working on.
When you start the job again,
you will return to where you left off.
Audio buttons allow you to play,
pause,
or replay the text on any screen.
On the main task screen, the audio buttons allow
you to play, pause, or replay the
instructions at the top of the screen.
The progress bar at the bottom of the main task
screen tracks how far along you are in the job.
Now let’s review the main tabs at the bottom of
the screen and what they mean.
The sitemap tab gives you a quick overall view
of the different components of the job.
The help tab provides basic guidance
on using the simulation.
The rules tab provides reference material to help
you complete the job,
including alphabetic filing Rules
1 through 10 and Cross-Referencing Rules.
The exit tab allows you to leave the simulation
at any time.
When you return,
the simulation will remember where you left off
and return you to your place.
Once you have completed a job,
you can submit your work for grading
by clicking the Finish and Submit button.
The Finish and Submit button is inactive
until you have filed all of the records in the job.
Before you submit your work
you are encouraged to take advantage of the
“Review Answers” button.
This brings you back to the main task screen
and allows you to review or change
your answers.
Then,
after you have reviewed your answers,
click “Finish and Submit” again.
When you are ready,
submit your final answers for scoring
by clicking on the “Submit” button.
After you have submitted your work,
you will be able to review your score
and the time it took you to complete the simulation.
Clicking on the
“Check Answers” button
allows you to look at a detailed analysis
of your answers,
so you can see how your score was calculated.
After you are done reviewing your score,
click the “Click Here to Close” button
to close out of the completed job.