Welcome to Job 13
This video walk through shows the different
tasks you will complete in this job
In Job 13
you will file 27 name cards into geographic order
using a geographic file by the
location name guide plan
When you start Job 13
before you begin your tasks
you will see the general information
screen for Job 13
The general information screen provides you
with information on how to code and
file records in geographic order
It is highly recommended that you read the
information before starting the job
Once you are in the job
if you need to refer back
to the information on this screen
there will be a General Information
button that allows you to review this screen
Click Next to begin Job 13
To begin coding the necessary units on each card
click the “Code: Step 1” button
Your cursor will turn into a slash mark
with a circle around it.
Click between each separate unit
to place a slash mark
To delete an existing slash mark
simply click on it again
Click on the forward and back arrows
to move between cards
Next, click on the “Code: Step 2 (units)” button
to identify the correct sequence of the filing units
At first, your cursor will look like an underline
Click on the primary unit, or key unit, to underline it
Once you have identified the primary unit
your cursor will change into the number 2
Click on the second unit to identify it.
Code the remaining units by clicking on each unit
in order to place the correct number
If you discover that you have made an error
click on any underlined or numbered unit again
to remove the number from that unit
and all units that follow it.
Continue to number the units on all
cards until you have completed the set
If you want to return to the General Information
screen to review geographic filing
click the General Information screen
When you are done reviewing the information
click the close button
to return to where you were in the job
Once you have finished coding
drag and drop each card into the correct folder
for a rough sort
The “Finish & Submit” button will remain disabled
until all records have been filed within folders
Next, open each folder to perform a
fine sort of the cards in that folder
To move a card
place your cursor in the white space
and hold the left mouse button down
to drag it into the correct order
Note that the number above each card
indicates the current order of the cards
For a zoomed-in view of the card
click anywhere on the card
When you are done viewing the card
click the close button
If you notice while you are sorting that you have
made a coding or filing error
click the blue arrow in the corner of the card
This will return the card back
to the main task screen
and you can fix the error and re-file
Once you have finished coding
filing, and sorting all records
click the “Finish & Submit” button
to submit your work for scoring
If you are not ready to finalize your answers
you are encouraged to take
advantage of the “Review Answers” button
This will bring you back to the main task screen
to review or change your answers
When you are ready
click the “Finish & Submit” button again
Click on the “Submit” button
to submit your final answers for scoring
After you have submitted your work
you will see your score
and the time it took you to complete the simulation
For a detailed review
click the “Check Answers” button
to compare your answers to the correct answers
After you have reviewed your answers
click the X to close the compare answers screen
When you are ready
click the “Click Here to Close” button
to close Job 13 and leave the simulation
Note that the “Check Answers” screen will NOT
be available for your review after you close Job 13